<strings>
<!-- FIRST TIME -->
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="disturb">I... I'm sorry to disturb you, sir...</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="dont-sorry">Oh... Don't be sorry, honey... I knew you would do it sooner or later...</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="mean">What... What do you mean...</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="want-out">You really want to get out, right?</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="mission">Yes... I came here in an important mission... I need to find...</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="give-shit">I don't give a shit about what you came here for, you know?</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="sorry-mean">Oh... I'm sorry... I mean...</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="know-works">Come on, honey... I know what you want... I know how this works... By your looks, I thought you'd have some good money to buy your way out of here..</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="i-have">I have, but... Not here...</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="shame">Now that's a shame... This is a very stressfull work, you know... But the 'tips' I receive from prisioners usually make it worth...</s>
<s id="relax">As you don't have any money... If you could do something to help me relax, then I could help with you lack of freedom problem...</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="foot-massage">To relax... Like... a foot massage...  I studied the ancient technique once... I don't be tickling or nothing....</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="cock">Really... How about you massage my cock?</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="oh">Oh...</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="subtle">What? Not subtle enough to you? Sorry, but I'm tired of your bullshit...</s>
<s id="help-you">I'll help you... Here... Look at this...</s>
<s id="hands-down">Get your hands down here and start working your technique... earn your freedom...</s>

<!--- Warder -->
<s id="far">Hey... You won't be able to work well from that far... Come closer...</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="happening">I can't believe this is happening to me...</s>
<s id="what-am-i-doing">_What am I doing... I never even touched one these..._</s>
<s id="stranger">_... and now I'm about to do it... with a stranger..._</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="bite">Come on... It won't bite you... Don't you want to get out of here?</s>
<s id="yeah-come">Yeah... Come here... I can already feel the heat of your fingers...</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="look-that">Oh, Lord... Look at that thing...</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="first">Hey... This is not your first time doig this, is it? Just get a good grip of it...</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="forcing">Why are you forcing me to do this?</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="not-forcing">I ain't forcing you anything, honey... You called me here, remember?</s>
<s id="get-started">Now get started or I will give up on our agreement...</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="forgive">_Forgive me, father..._</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="nice">Yeeeeaah... You have a nice touch, honey... Look what you did...</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="this">_This thing is... is... It feels like..._</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="progress">Uuuhh... So... We won't have much progress like this...</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="what-mean">What do you mean...</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="moves">Come on, now... Show me your moves...</s>
<s id="natural">That's nice, honey... You are a natural...</s>
<s id="faster-1">How about speed up the pace, now...</s>
<s id="faster-2">Come on... Faster, honey...</s>
<s id="keep">Very good... Now keep the pace for me...</s>

<!--- Warder -->
<s id="awesome">This is awesome, honey... Now... Give me a show of your tits... It will help me finish this faster...</s>
<s id="sigh-fine">Sigh... Fine... You're doing a good job and I'm about to finish this anyways...</s>
<s id="good-girl">Good girl... Good girl...</s>

<s id="act-bicth">So... You wanna act like a bitch? I can be nasty too...</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="no">What are you doing...</s>
<s id="dare">Don't you dare put this shirt down... With your lousy job I'll need a visual aid to finish...</s>

<s id="OBEY">OBEY</s>
<s id="NOT-OBEY">DISOBEY</s>

<!--- Warder -->
<s id="oh-man">Oh man... This is it... Hold tight...</s>




<!--- Warder -->
<s id="hand-score-5">Such obedient girl... Continue like this and you will go far, honey...</s>
<s id="hand-score-4">Thanks, honey... You have a talent...</s>
<s id="hand-score-3">Thanks, honey... You have a talent...</s>
<s id="hand-score-2">Thanks, honey... You have a talent...</s>
<s id="hand-score-1">You have to learn how to respect your man, girl...</s>
<s id="hand-score-0">You have to learn how to respect your man, girl...</s>
<!--- Lara -->
<s id="can-leave">Can I leave now?</s>
<!--- Warder -->
<s id="worked">Yeah... You'll got your payment...</s>
<s id="walk">I'll take a walk out there for a few minutes... If some prisioner happen to escape now, no one would notice...</s>

<!--- Lara -->
<s id="whats-this">Oh lord... My hand...</s>
<s id="gift">Yeah... Another reward for your hard work... Make a good use of it...</s>
<s id="see-ya">Don't be long, now... I hope you see you again... People are always leaving and coming back, you know...</s>



<!-- SECOND TIME -->
<s id="leave-again">I... I... need to leave again...</s>
<s id="i-know">I know you do, honey... And you know what you need to do in order to get released, right? You did it once...</s>
<s id="do-again">If... If I do that thing again... Then can I leave?</s>
<s id="ask-properly">Wait... You need to ask properly... I don't know what 'that thing' means...</s>
<s id="saying">Come on... I wanna hear you saying it...</s>
<s id="oh-lord">_Oh Lord..._</s>
<s id="massage-penis">If I... If I massage... your... penis... would you let me leave?</s>
<s id="no-wont">No, I won't...</s>
<s id="what">What?</s>
<s id="second-time">I know you're eager to put your hands in my cock again... But each time you ask me to turn a blind eye and let you go, the price gets higher...</s>
<s id="blow-me">You'll have to blow me this time, honey....</s>
<s id="fan">Blow you? You mean... Because it's so hot in here? Wouldn't it be easier to get a fan?</s>
<s id="so-cute">So cute...</s>
<s id="suck">What I mean is that you'll have to suck my cock...</s>
<s id="direct">Ha... I love the face you do when I start being direct...</s>
<s id="business">Now come over here... It's time to earn your freedom again...</s>
<s id="get-started-2">Well... Let's get started... Get me prepped first...</s>
<s id="missed">Aaah... Did you miss my cock? Because I missed your touch...</s>
<s id="doing-again">I... I can't believe I'm doing this again...</s>
<s id="get-used">I'm sure you're already getting used to do this...</s>

<s id="PULL-SHIRT">PULL SIHRT UP</s>
<s id="CORRUPTION">CORRUPTION</s>
<s id="BEG-LEAVE">BEG TO NOT BLOW HIM</s>
<s id="KEEP-WORKING">KEEP WORKING</s>

<s id="beg-1">Please, mister... I... I can't put this thing into my mouth... I... I'll keep stroking exactly the way you want...</s>
<s id="beg-2">I'll do it for hours if want... But, please... Don't make me put this in my mouth...</s>
<s id="beg-3">If you want to keep giving me handjobs here every day, I'll be delighted to agree...</s>
<s id="beg-4">But if you want to leave this cell... You're going to so suck my cock...</s>
<s id="beg-5">Now, back to work!</s>


<s id="even-ask">Good girl... I didn't even had to ask...</s>
<s id="doing-right">You see... You're already doing it right without even thinking about it...</s>
<s id="thought-would">I... I... thought you would...</s>
<s id="keep-nice">Shhh... Just keep your nice work...</s>
<s id="got-me-ready">Nice work, girl... You got me ready...</s>
<s id="taste">Now it's time for you to know the taste of cock...</s>

<s id="get-down-here-1">You'll need to get down a little more for this, honey...</s>
<s id="get-down-here-2">Come on... Don't get shy on me again...</s>
<s id="difficult-1">It's not that difficult, honey...</s>
<s id="difficult-2">Just touch it with your lips... As soon as you feel it, I'm sure you'll crave for more...</s>

<s id="tease-1">Oh my God... Stop being such a tease... I can already feel the heat of your breath...</s>
<s id="tease-2">Please... Don't make me do this... It is so degrading...</s>
<s id="tease-3">It's  not as degrading as rotting in this cell, honey... It's a skill every girl should develop to please a man...</s>
<s id="tease-4">Come on... Just open your mouth and start with the tip...</s>

<s id="suck-1">Yeeahh... That's it, honey...</s>
<s id="suck-2">Your lips feel so good... But it's time to go deeper...</s>
<s id="suck-3">So... How do you feel having a cock in your mouth?</s>
<s id="suck-4">Mnnnnngh mmng... Mnn..</s>
<s id="suck-5">Ha... I love when they try to talk like this...</s>
<s id="suck-6">Now... If you don't want a sore jaw and are willing to get your job done, you better get a bit more... intense....</s>
<s id="suck-7">Mnnnnngh?</s>
<s id="suck-8">Come on... Make an effort... Sequeze the joy out of my balls if you want to get out of here...</s>

<s id="hard-1">Yeeahh... This is how a good slut does it!</s>
<s id="hard-2">You should see your face now, honey... It's not even close to that cocky expression you used to show here...</s>
<s id="hard-3">MMMmmmnhhgg! MMMmmmnhhgg!</s>
<s id="hard-4">Oh, boy... You're the best... I'm getting close now...</s>
<s id="hard-5">Fuuuuck... That's it, honey... Do you wan't it in your face or in your throat?</s>

<s id="FACE">FACE</s>
<s id="THROAT">THROAT</s>
<s id="NO-STOP">JUST STOP!</s>

<s id="mmm">Mnnnnngh!!!</s>
<s id="what-say">What did you said?</s>
<s id="full">Oh... I forgot you can't speak with a mouth full... Guess I'll have to choose it myself...</s>
<s id="cooomes">Now, here it cooooomes...</s>

<s id="dropping">Oh, come on... You're dropping everything on the floor...</s>
<s id="disgusting">What... What was I supposed to do with this disgusting thing?</s>
<s id="mouth">Disgusting? You can spill all you want, but some will remain in your mouth... And I bet you'll learn to love it when you remember the taste later...</s>
<s id="bastard">Bastard... How could you do this to me...</s>
<s id="can-go-now-1">Whatever, honey... I hope you come back sometime, so we can have even more fun...</s>
<s id="can-go-now-2">You can leave after cleaning the mess you made in my floor... See ya!</s>


</strings>