<strings>
<!--Player-->
<s id="what-up">Hey... What's up, Alfred?</s>
<!--Winston-->
<s id="stop-addr">Mister <d character="Player" data="TXT_NAME"/>, I must ask you to cease addressing me by that name... I have requested that several times now...</s>
                                    
<!--Player-->
<s id="dont-fret">Hey... Don't fret, man... It's just a joke... Don't you get it?</s>
<!--Winston-->
<s id="i-get-it">Of course I get it... The kind of humor a man enjoys tells a lot about his character...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="charming">Very charming... Aren't you happy to finally have a work colleague in this big ass house?</s>

<!--Winston-->
<s id="im-touched">I'm touched by your concerns about me, but I never felt lonely in this manor...</s>
<s id="her-presence">Miss <d character="Lara" data="TXT_SURNAME"/>'s presence is already pleasant enough for me... Your being here only disturbs my chances of enjoying her delightful company...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="i-know-mean">Uhmm... A 'pleasant' and 'delightful' presence... I think I know what you mean...</s>
<!--Winston-->
<s id="respectfully">Respectfully serving Miss <d character="Lara" data="TXT_SURNAME" /> doesn't forbid me to feast my eyes on her stunning figure...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="i-see">Yeah... I see...</s>

<!--Winston-->
<s id="stop-pestering">Please, stop pestering me...</s>

<!--CHOICE-->
<s id="between-us-c">Do you jack off thinking about her?</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="between-us">Between us guys... You must have been jacking off a lot while thinking about her all these years working here, right?</s>
<!--Winston-->
<s id="first">First... There aren't that many years since she came to a 'legal' age and I'd never masturbate thinking about an underage girl...</s>
<s id="second">Second... My sex life doesn't concern you...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="problems">Well... Both of your points have problems... But about the second one, I'm pretty sure masturbation doesn't count as 'sex life'...</s>

<!--CHOICE-->
<s id="parties">She probably throws wild parties in this place...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="this-place">This place... I bet <d character="Lara" data="TXT_NAME" /> has been throwing some wild parties around here, right?</s>
<!--Winston-->
<s id="reserved">No... Miss <d character="Lara" data="TXT_SURNAME" /> is a quite reserved person... She receives a friend or two here sometimes, but her nights are always spent on books and research...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="virgin">Jesus... So she actually has no... experience...</s>

<!--Winston-->
<s id="confirm">Well... I can neither confirm nor deny that... But I can say she gets very uncomfortable every time something remotelly sexual is mentioned near her...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="cute">That's cute...</s>

<!--CHOICE-->
<s id="SEARCH-TABLE">SEARCH TABLE</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="think-table">Hum... I can see a lot of documents spread out on that table... That would be a good place to search for the automation system PIN... I wonder if...</s>
                                    
<s id="can-search">Hey... Can you give some space here? I want to check if there's something interesting on the table...</s>
                                    
<!-- Winston -->
<s id="no-table">Impossible... This is Miss <d character="Lara" data="TXT_SURNAME" suffix="'s" /> personal study table and she always tells me that it must be left alone...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="come-on">Oh, come on... It's not like...</s>
<!--Winston-->
<s id="dont-insist">Please, don't insist... It's my sacred duty to follow her instructions...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="lure-1">Damn... There must a be way to lure him away from this room...</s>
<s id="lure-2">If someone knocked on the main door he would need to leave for a few minutes... But how could I make it happen?</s>

<!-- CHOICE -->
<s id="choice-pool-1"><d character="Lara" data="TXT_NAME" /> asked you to 'prepare' the pool for her</s>
<s id="choice-pool-2">Hey, man... <d character="Lara" data="TXT_NAME" /> asked you to 'prepare' the pool for her... Whatever it means...</s>
<!--Winston-->
<s id="the-pool">The pool... I miss the days she went there every morning...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="bikini">Why? Does she always wear some hot bikini or something?</s>
<!--Winston-->
<s id="excuse">Humpf... It doesn't concern you... Now excuse me... I need to assist her...</s>
<!--Player-->
<s id="done-it-pool">Great! Now I can try to sneak into her bedroom!</s>

<!-- CHOICE -->
<s id="LEAVE">LEAVE</s>

<!-- Player -->
<s id="table-comment">Okay... Let's see if there's anything interesting around here...</s>
<s id="table-globe">The Earth... Depicted as a globe... To think that more and more people are triggered by this in the 21st century...</s>
<s id="table-empty-folders">It's pile of empty folders... Nothing to see there...</s>
<s id="table-book-1">Jesus... How many books is she able to lay around this house?</s>
<s id="table-book-under">Is there something under this one?</s>
<s id="table-book-under-condition">PERCEPTION (1+)</s>
<s id="table-book-piece">Whoah... This is not a toy... Does she like to walk around carrying pieces like that?</s>
<s id="table-book-client">My mysterious client might be right about her violent tendencies... But I'd better leave it alone for now...</s>
<s id="table-folder">Okay... This one looks promising...</s>
<s id="table-doc-nope-1">Nope...</s>
<s id="table-doc-nope-2">Boooring...</s>
<s id="table-doc-nope-3">Nothing here...</s>
<s id="table-doc-1">Yes! This paper says the automation system was installed just a few days ago! She probably never had the chance to change the default PIN!</s>
<s id="table-doc-2">Now I can try to unlock it at the computer terminal!</s>
<s id="table-doc-3">I already know the security PIN. I can try to unlock the automation system now!</s>
<s id="automation-doc">Congratulations, Miss <d character="Lara" data="TXT_SURNAME" />!\n
\n
Your home automation system was succefully installed  and is ready to use.\n
\n
Remember to change your initial security PIN to ensure maximum privacy and safety!\n
\n
Your security PIN is: &lt;size=23&gt;<d character="Player" data="TXT_AUTOMATION_PIN" />&lt;/size&gt;\n
</s>
<s id="BACK">BACK</s>


</strings>