<strings>
<s id="interview-1">Sigh... I wonder how long more I'll have to wait until...</s>
<s id="interview-2">Oh... Someone is coming...</s>
<s id="interview-3-h">Hey... What are you doing sitting there like an idiot?</s>
<s id="interview-4-h">What? You told me keep quiet waiting for...</s>
<s id="interview-5-h">Yeah, yeah... Whatever... Didn't you see The Boss arived? You can have fun with him at his office now... Move it!</s>
<s id="interview-3-m">Hey, girl... The Boss has arived... You can come into his office now...</s>
<s id="interview-4-m">Oh... Okay... Thank you...</s>
<s id="interview-5-m">Yeah... Tell The Boss I treated you right, okay...</s>

<s id="interview-6-ini">_Oh my God... There he is... I hope I'm well prepared for this..._</s>
<s id="interview-6">Hello, mister...</s>
<s id="interview-7">.........</s>
<s id="interview-8">I'm, uhh... I'm here for the meeting... I believe it was scheduled for today, right?</s>
<s id="interview-9">.........</s>
<s id="interview-10">Uhh... Can you hear me, mister? My name is...</s>
<s id="interview-11-s">Fuck's sake...</s>
<s id="interview-11">I can hear you, and I already know your fucking name...</s>
<s id="interview-12">I can't even relax for a few minutes without having some stupid bitch babbling on my neck...</s>
<s id="interview-13">I.. I'm sorry...  I tought I was supposed to...</s>
<s id="interview-14">Yeah, yeah... I know why you are here... Probably more than you know yourself...</s>
<s id="interview-15">So why don't you relax? I'll be with you in a few seconds...</s>
<s id="interview-16">I... uuhh.........</s>
<s id="interview-17-t">Are you deaf or retarded?? Didn't your hear when I...</s>
<s id="interview-17-t-1">I..... you...</s>
<s id="interview-17-t-2">You look... just like my little Lisa...</s>
<s id="interview-17-t-2-l">_Yes... The makeup effect is working..._</s>
<s id="interview-17-t-3">She started painting her face just like this after I started spending all nights in her bedroom when we were young...</s>
<s id="interview-17-t-4">Her bed was so small that my body occupied most of the space... She kept shivering during the night so I had to hold her tight, give her my heat, and... and...</s>
<s id="interview-17-t-5-1">Yes... I remember... That fragile little thing completely submitted to me...</s>
<s id="interview-17-t-5-2">Daaaaammnn... That was gooood...</s>
<s id="interview-17-t-6">_Jesus Christ... Someone has to put a bullet into this creep's head..._</s>
<s id="interview-17-t-7">Urgh... Just... Just sit there so we can talk...</s>

<s id="interview-17-nt-1">Are you deaf or retarded?? Didn't your hear when I told you to fucking sit?</s>
<s id="interview-17-nt-2">I... I didn't know if...</s>
<s id="interview-17-nt-3">Look at your stupid face...</s>
<s id="interview-17-nt-4">Yeah... You look just like the typical girl who doesn't know much about nothing...</s>
<s id="interview-17-nt-5">You think your pretty face is enough to earn you some respect?</s>
<s id="interview-17-nt-5-mu">Can't you see how you look even more stupid with that whore makeup of yours?</s>
<s id="interview-17-nt-6">.......</s>
<s id="interview-17-nt-6-mu">_Oh no... I did something wrong about the makeup..._</s>
<s id="interview-17-nt-7">Sigh... I didn't had a very good first impression of you, girl... You're going to make up for it until the end of this meeting...</s>
<s id="interview-17-nt-8">Now sit on the couch so we can talk... You can understand this simple instruction, right?</s>

<s id="interview-b-1">So... You're aware that we'll have an important auction here tonight, right?</s>
<s id="interview-b-2">Yes... Yes, I know...</s>
<s id="interview-b-3">And do you know your role at this event?</s>

<s id="interview-b-4-h">I'm... I'm supposed to work as a hostess, right?</s>
<s id="interview-b-5-h">Yes... You'll just need to be pretty, wear a nice respectable dress, smile to the guests and guide the buyers to the safe room where they can collect their items...</s>
<s id="interview-b-6-h">It's a job so simple that even you can do it, right?</s>
<s id="interview-b-7-h">Yes... I... I'm able to do that...</s>
<s id="interview-b-8-h">We'll see...</s>

<s id="interview-b-4-m">I... I think I know, but... I'm not sure...</s>
<s id="interview-b-5-m">Ha ha ha... Poor thing... Totally clueless... Looks like you didn't suspected the sad face on your daddy when he sent you all the way here... Or maybe he simply doesn't care...</s>
<s id="interview-b-6-m">My... daddy?</s>
<s id="interview-b-7-m">That sucker has millions in overdue debt of to our group... And, of course, the only way he found to pay was by offering his pretty daughter to be sold at the auction...</s>
<s id="interview-b-8-m">Sell!?!? Me!?!?!</s>
<s id="interview-b-9-m">Yeah... There are several buyers interested in girls like you... You can only hope one of the few nice ones offer the highest bid for you...</s>
<s id="interview-b-10-m">But... I'm not... I'm not...</s>
<s id="interview-b-11-m">Yes, you are... Your job will be to walk in around wearing some skimpy clothing during the auction to get the buyers interested and then wait for your new owner at the safe room...</s>
<s id="interview-b-12-m">_I...  At least I'll have access to the safe room where I can find the Goddess Slab... But looks like this 'owner' thing will be a serious problem..._</s>

<s id="canteen-1">Now give me a second... Before we continue to next phase of this meeting, I'll need to clear my throat...</s>
<s id="canteen-a-1">Huh? Where the fuck is my canteen?</s>
<s id="canteen-a-2">_Oh no... I forgot to put the canteen back on it's place..._</s>
<s id="canteen-a-3">MOTHERFUCKER!!</s>
<s id="canteen-a-4">When I find the scumbag who took my canteen I'm going rip out his heart...</s>
<s id="canteen-a-5">Sigh... Looks like I'll have to continue this meeting with a dry throat...</s>

<s id="canteen-2">Ahh... I need a good sip of that juice to fill up my tank...</s>
<s id="canteen-b-1">....</s>
<s id="canteen-b-2">Uurgh.... Who the fuck... cof... filled... my canteen with beer?</s>
<s id="canteen-b-3">It tastes so good, but... UUurrghh...</s>
<s id="canteen-b-4">I... I can already fell the heat rising in my body... I was not supposed to drink that shit ever again...</s>
<s id="canteen-b-5">...... ooohh shit...</s>
<s id="canteen-b-6">Urf... Whatever... We... We must continue with the meeting...</s>

<s id="canteen-c-1">Buuuuuurp...</s>
<s id="canteen-c-2">Yeah... My juice always help me to get psyched up when I need it...</s>
<s id="canteen-c-3">I need to refill the hallway water cooler with more of this...</s>
<s id="canteen-c-4">_Oh... He filled that water cooler with this disgusting juice!?_</s>
<s id="canteen-c-5">For now... I'm just ready to kick shit up and can continue with this meeting...</s>

<s id="interview-c-1">Now... There's one final important topic to discus...</s>

<s id="interview-c-h-1">I should have mentioned earlier that this hostess job also requires you to perform another important role...</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-2">What... are... you talking about?</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-3">You know... As a leader of this military group in Uswana, I need to display a serious persona to all bidders during the auction... A serious persona... A man of family...</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-4">I... don't... understand...</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-5">You can't be so stupid... I need to show up at the auction with a wife... And you look like the perfect one to play the part...</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-6">What?!?</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-7">Yeah, girl... I want to display a beautiful and skilled wife down there... A girl I can brag about to the high players...</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-8">So... we'll need to... you know... do some 'wife-husband rehearsal'...</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-9">No... wait... you can't just...</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-10">I can do whatever the fuck I want, bitch... Refusal is not an option...</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-11">We will do husband-wife trainining now... So I can learn wich good qualities you have...</s>
<s id="interview-c-h-12">What about you make our life easy and tell me some good wife skill you have before we get started?</s>

<s id="interview-c-m-1">During my years managing a corporate office I learned an important lesson... Quality control is essential...</s>
<s id="interview-c-m-2">Which means I need to be sure that all our products are on perfect conditions for sale...</s>
<s id="interview-c-m-3">I... don't... understand...</s>
<s id="interview-c-m-4">You know what your future owner expect from you, right? I need to make sure he will be statisfied with the quality of the product...</s>
<s id="interview-c-m-5">Owner?!? Quality?!? I'm a person... You can't treat people as objects...</s>
<s id="interview-c-m-6">So cute... You'll get used to it...</s>
<s id="interview-c-m-7">You... You can't do this to me... to anyone...</s>
<s id="interview-c-m-8">I can do whatever the fuck I want, bitch...</s>
<s id="interview-c-m-9">Just accept the fact that you'll be selled as fuck meat...</s>
<s id="interview-c-m-10">Or do you happen to have any other skill that could be used by your owner?</s>


<s id="interview-c-10">My... skills...</s>
<s id="interview-condition-y">FOUND A CERTAIN DIARY PAGE</s>
<s id="interview-condition-n">DID NOT FOUND A CERTAIN DIARY PAGE</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese">CAN SPEAK JAPANESE</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese-1">I... I can speak Japanese...</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese-2">Huh?</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese-3">Kon'nichiwa... Watashinonamaeha <d character="Lara" suffix="..." /> Ogenkidesuka...</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese-4">Oh shit... No way... No way... You gotta be fucking kidding...</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese-5">Kono basho wa akushū ga suru. Anata wa byōnindeari, hontōni anata ga shinu koto o negatte imasu...</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese-6-h">It can't be... Not just a wife, but... A real waifu... oh, man... ooooohhh... man...</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese-6-m">It can't be... A real waifu sex slave... so hot... so hot... oh, man... ooooohhh... man...</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese-7">Byōki no hentai ga watashi kara hanarete kudasai!!!!</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese-8">Phew... Enough with the show, girl... That's really an awesome skill... You almost se me on fire...</s>
<s id="interview-c-japanese-9">What? Oh no... Oh no... You were supposed to... to...</s>

<s id="interview-c-silent">STAY SILENT</s>
<s id="interview-c-silent-1">I... I... Uuuuhh.........</s>
<s id="interview-c-silent-2-h">Jesus Christ... Nothing but air in your head? Looks like I'll need to settle only for the looks in your case...</s>
<s id="interview-c-silent-3-h">Well... I don't care... Most of my guests would dream with a mindless bimbo wife like you...</s>
<s id="interview-c-silent-2-m">You see? Nothing but air in your head...</s>
<s id="interview-c-silent-3-m">A live sex doll... Just like what the buyers expect...</s>

<s id="interview-c-arch">ARCHAEOLOGY</s>
<s id="interview-c-arch-1">I... I'm an archaeologist?</s>
<s id="interview-c-arch-2-h">Pffft... A girl with a degree?</s>
<s id="interview-c-arch-3-h">As my wife, you would know your place... No useless college education...</s>
<s id="interview-c-arch-2-m">Pffft... A degree?</s>
<s id="interview-c-arch-3-m">As a good slave, you should know your place... Education won't have no use in your new life...</s>
<s id="interview-c-arch-4">So... You will just forget about that archaeology shit from now on...</s>



<s id="interview-win">No no no... Stop the moonspeak!!! It's going to happen... I can't hold it... I can't hold it!!!</s>
<s id="interview-win-0">You did it, <d character="Lara" suffix="..." /> He's gonna pop!</s>
<s id="interview-win-1">Anata ga daikirai!!!! Chikushou!!!</s>
<s id="interview-win-2">Nooo... ahnnnnnggg.....</s>
<s id="interview-win-3">Eeeww!! Gross!!</s>
<s id="interview-win-4">Oh no... Oh no... I'm sorry, miss... I didn't want to make a mess...</s>
<s id="interview-win-5">Oh my God... This is disgusting...</s>
<s id="interview-win-6">No, miss... sob.. sob... Don't be mean... sob... sob... Don't look... Don't look...</s>
<s id="interview-win-7">Damn... You really flipped a switch in the head of this psycho...</s>
<s id="interview-win-8">I couldn't do it without your help, <d character="Player" suffix="..." /></s>
<s id="interview-win-8-choose-0">You can push him now to get your life easier during the auction... But we can't demand too much or his men might become suspicious...</s>
<s id="interview-win-8-choose-1">Remember... You still need a disguise to get into the safe room... And now that you dominated him, you can choose again your role in the auction...</s>
<s id="interview-win-8-choose-2">Going disguised as hostess is more dignifying... But also means a guard will follow you to the safe room with the Goddess Slab buyer...</s>
<s id="interview-win-8-choose-3">You'll have to find a way to get rid of two guys before escaping with the Goddess Slab...</s>
<s id="interview-win-8-choose-4">Going disguised as a... girl to be sold........ Well, it's not exactly pleasant...</s>
<s id="interview-win-8-choose-5">But the buyer will certainly ask for... 'privacy'... when he comes for you in the safe room... So there will be only one rich guy with no military training to get rid of...</s>
<s id="interview-win-8-2">It's still scary, but... But I must to take advantage of his state...</s>
<s id="interview-win-9">_I'm sorry... I'm sorry... I won't make no mess anymore... Don't punish me like mommy used to..._</s>
<s id="interview-win-10-a">Now just keep crushing this bastard!</s>
<s id="interview-win-10-a-0">Yes... He doesn't deserve any mercy...</s>
<s id="interview-win-10-a-1">Hey! You pathetic sad excuse of a man!</s>
<s id="interview-win-10-a-2">No... Please don't hurt me, miss... _Please_</s>
<s id="interview-win-10-a-3">Here... Take this... It's all I have with me... I swear... swear...</s>
<s id="interview-win-10-a-4">Pfft... I don't want your garbage... I need you to do something for me...</s>

<s id="interview-win-10-b">Now take it easy... You're better than him...</s>
<s id="interview-win-10-b-0">You're right, <d character="Player" suffix="..." /> Thank you... I'm not the kind of person who abuses sick and weak people...</s>
<s id="interview-win-10-b-1">Now... You've been displaying an awful behavior, sir... If you want to apologise then there's a favor I need from you...</s>
<s id="interview-win-10-b-2">Yes... I'll do... I'll do anything... Just don't tell anyone about this...</s>
<s id="interview-win-11">I need to get into the safe room, NOW!</s>
<s id="interview-win-12">I'm sorry, miss... The safe room is time locked... It's the Bulls head-office policy... I can't do anything about that...</s>
<s id="interview-win-13">Damn it... Looks like I'll really have to wait until the end of the auction...</s>
<s id="interview-win-14-a">Listen up, loser!</s>
<s id="interview-win-14-a-1">Sob... sob... yes, mistress...</s>
<s id="interview-win-14-b">Another favor then...</s>
<s id="interview-win-14-b-1">Yes... I'll do... I'll do...</s>


<s id="interview-win-14">You'll contact your men and tell them to not harass me...</s>
<s id="interview-win-14-h">Tell them that I'm going to work as a hostess during the auction... Make it clear to them that I'll be the one who follows the buyer of that ancient artifact to the safe room...</s>
<s id="interview-win-14-m">Even being just a girl to be 'sold' during the auction... I must be left alone!!</s>
<s id="interview-win-14-2">And you'll to stay locked in this office the whole night... Do you understand?</s>
<s id="interview-win-15">Locked here? But I'm afraid of being alone and...</s>
<s id="interview-win-16">You'll do exactly what I said or I'll tell everyone about the mess you made during this meeting...</s>
<s id="interview-win-17">Nooooooo... Don't tell anyone... I'll do everything you said... I swear...</s>
<s id="interview-win-18">Sigh... That's it... At least I'll have access to the auction...</s>
<s id="interview-win-19">This creep won't be a problem anymore... But I'll need to keep the disguise in order to fool the rest of his men...</s>
<s id="interview-win-20">So I'd better stick to the plan and wait for the auction oustide...</s>


<s id="interview-c-2">.........</s>
<s id="interview-c-3">Now... You know I'm talking about much more interesting skills... So quit the whining and stop trying to get far from me...</s>
<s id="interview-c-4">Sir... Maybe... it would be better if we... continue this meeting another day and...</s>
<s id="interview-c-5">You just don't get it, do you? Looks like someone here still have a lot to learn...</s>
<s id="interview-c-6">Jeez... You have such a pretty face... Wouldn't it be a shame if it ends up filled with nasty scars?</s>
<s id="interview-c-7">You... You are scaring me, sir... Can I leave now?</s>
<s id="interview-c-8-h">Leave? You came into here by your own will... And you knew what this job is about...</s>
<s id="interview-c-8-m">Leave? Don't forget you're property of the Freedom Bulls until the auction... There's no place for you to 'leave' to...</s>
<s id="interview-c-9">Come here...</s>
<s id="interview-c-10-h">You see... I really need some quality time with my 'wife'... And you need this job, right?</s>
<s id="interview-c-10-m">You see... The 'quality control' test I need to perform is really important...</s>
<s id="interview-c-11">So... Just welcome whatever I'm planning to do with you, and I will even give you a little reward before the auction... It won't take much long...</s>
<s id="interview-c-12-yes">SUBMIT</s>
<s id="interview-c-12-no">NO WAY</s>

<s id="lost-1-s">Then... please... just be... gentle...</s>
<s id="lost-2-s">Good to see you listen to reason...</s>
<s id="lost-3-s">However, saying I'll be gentle might be a bit of a strech...</s>
<s id="lost-1">I don't want any reward... I.. I just want to go...</s>
<s id="lost-2">Sigh... Trying to play the innocent won't earn you anything... You can't leave this room or even this building without my approval...</s>
<s id="lost-3">But if you prefer the hard way, so be it...</s>
<s id="lost-4">Just check these nice soft lips you have...</s>
<s id="lost-5-h">I think it's time for my beautiful wife put them to proper use...</s>
<s id="lost-5-m">Your new owner will use them a lot, so I think it's just fair for me to test them first...</s>
<s id="lost-5">_no... please... don't do this..._</s>
<s id="lost-5-s">.......... yes...... sir...</s>
<s id="lost-6">Just shut up and come down, here... NOW!</s>

<s id="lost-7-h">See? This is the position my pretty wife needs to keep to make me happy when I come home...</s>
<s id="lost-7-m">See? This is the position you'll show keep to show your new owner that you belong to him... You'd better know your place...</s>
<s id="lost-8-s">.......... this is so... degrading...</s>
<s id="lost-9-s">Ha... You will still know what being degraded really is about...</s>
<s id="lost-8-s-cs">_I can't believe I'm doing this again..._</s>
<s id="lost-9-s-cs">So are you used to suck cock? Don't worry... I'm sure you'll learn something new today...</s>
<s id="lost-8">_..... no, sir... please, let me go..._</s>
<s id="lost-9">Sigh... Looks like there's only one way to make you shut the fuck up...</s>
<s id="lost-8-cs">..... no, please... not this again...</s>
<s id="lost-9-cs">Sigh... Looks like there's only one way to make you shut the fuck up...</s>
<s id="lost-10">Let's not waste more of my time, then...</s>
<s id="lost-11">mmmpf... what are... mmmpf... you doing...</s>
<s id="lost-12">You have to work this jaw of yours, girl... There's a lot of meat for it to handle here...</s>
<s id="lost-13">mmmpf... not... mmmpf... not like this...</s>
<s id="lost-14">Damn... Can you still talk!?</s>
<s id="lost-15">But I know how to fix it...</s>
<s id="lost-16">Ha... I bet you can't speak now, can you?</s>
<s id="lost-17">mmmm!!! mmmm!!</s>
<s id="lost-18">As I expected... Now I'll have some peace...</s>
<s id="lost-19-h">Hummm... Soft lips, warm wet mouth... You have all the main qualities a girl needs to become my wife...</s>
<s id="lost-19-m">Hummm... Soft lips, warm wet mouth... Maybe I'll buy you myself...</s>
<s id="lost-20">You can come live with me after the auction... What do you think?</s>
<s id="lost-21">mmmm!!! mmmm!!</s>
<s id="lost-22">Yeah... I knew you'd accept my proposal...</s>
<s id="lost-23">But now that we warmed up... It's time to check how much you can take...</s>
<s id="lost-24">mmmm mmm?!?!?</s>
<s id="lost-25">Yeah... Take a deep breath now...</s>
<s id="lost-26">coff... coff... coff... are you... coff... coff... insane?!?!?!</s>
<s id="lost-27">Whoah... You should have seen the nice buldge you had on your throat...</s>
<s id="lost-28">Most girls can't take it full for the first time without fainting... But looks like you're a natural!</s>
<s id="lost-29">you... you can't...</s>
<s id="lost-30">Shit... Are you already speaking again?</s>
<s id="lost-31">Well... I'm already on fire... And I think I can improve your skill...</s>
<s id="lost-32">So let's train you to get rid of the gag reflex...</s>
<s id="lost-33">What?!?!</s>
<s id="lost-34">Yeah... That's what I'm talking about...</s>
<s id="lost-34-m1">Hey... You ruined your stupid makeup... You're looking just like the way I love...</s>
<s id="lost-34-m2">... and now your lipstick is spread all over my cock... you'll gonna have to clean it up, bitch...</s>
<s id="lost-35">The nasty sounds you're making are music to ears...</s>
<s id="lost-36">Damn... Fucking your mouth is so good...</s>
<s id="lost-37">Oh, man... Get back to the couch... I have to finish this in great style...</s>
<s id="lost-38">Lay here... Legs over there...</s>
<s id="lost-39">Why... why are you making me lie here like this?</s>
<s id="lost-40">Can't you guess? I think even you can understand how we'll finish this...</s>
<s id="lost-41">You... You can't possibly be thinking about... about...</s>
<s id="lost-42">Shhh shhh shhh... Don't worry... It all be over soon...</s>
<s id="lost-43-h">It's time to show you what really means to be my wife...</s>
<s id="lost-43-m">It's time to show you what really means to be property of someone...</s>
<s id="lost-43-tt">Let me also get a good view of these tits...</s>
<s id="lost-44">Oh my God... This is not happenig... This is not happening...</s>
<s id="lost-45">Ha... Trying to deny the reality is really for the desperate, girl... But this is totally happening...</s>
<s id="lost-46">Go hide into your happy place if you must...</s>
<s id="lost-47">...... what kind of man are you... you pig... you... you can't treat women like this...</s>
<s id="lost-48">Well... You're probably right... But I'm the kind of man who doesn't play by the rules...</s>
<s id="lost-49">Besides... There're actually some girls who love to be handled this way... You'll never know if you are one until you try it, right?</s>
<s id="lost-50">mmmphhf mmppfhh!!!</s>
<s id="lost-51">See? The way you instinctively started to suck my finger like a pacifier... I think you actually will love this...</s>
<s id="lost-52">Whffatt?? No... mmph... I'mmphh... juspth tryinpgh to spheakk...</s>
<s id="lost-53">Yeah... You have this irritating habit of non stop speaking...</s>
<s id="lost-54">But I'm sick of this chit chat... It's time for some hardcore fun...</s>
<s id="lost-55">Yeeahh... This is the good life...</s>
<s id="lost-56-h">You know... I used to need a tight grip to be able to fuck my ex-wife like this... Bitch kept struggling every damn time...</s>
<s id="lost-57-h">But you are taking it like a princess...</s>
<s id="lost-56-m">You know... I usually have a much harder time when I need to 'break' a girl that is about to be selled in one of our actions...</s>
<s id="lost-57-m">But you are already accepting it like a good slave should do...</s>
<s id="lost-58">Oh man... Your mouth is great... But these tits also feel nice...</s>
<s id="lost-59">I'll definetively play more with them during our next metting...</s>
<s id="lost-60">Can you feel how your throat learned to stretch to accept my cock? It's something your body won't forget...</s>
<s id="lost-61">I can almost see it expanding your insides...</s>
<s id="lost-62">Uuurrg... But I can hold it much longer... so let's get this done...</s>
<s id="lost-63">Are you still there, girl? I know being fucked like also screws with the person's mind...</s>
<s id="lost-64">Now get ready... I'll pump a lot of seed right into your stomach!</s>
<s id="lost-65">Daaamn... I think you'll gonna be burping my cum for a couple of days after that...</s>
<s id="lost-66">Phew... You can fix your clothes now... We're done here...</s>
<s id="lost-66-reward-1">I promised you a reward if you submitted to me, right?</s>
<s id="lost-66-reward-2">Here... You can have this...</s>
<s id="lost-66-reward-3">Ammunition is getting very scarce these days in Uswana...</s>
<s id="lost-66-reward-4">You can exchange for money and buy you shoes, clothes or whatever the fuck you girls seem always so interested in...</s>
<s id="lost-67">................</s>
<s id="lost-68">Huh!? Are you still there?</s>
<s id="lost-69">................</s>
<s id="lost-70">Ha... Not so talkative now, huh? Yeah... I usually cause this effect on my girls...</s>
<s id="lost-71">Well... You can recover there for a few minutes...</s>
<s id="lost-72">When you come back to reality, go cleanup the mess on your face and wait for the auction outside...</s>
<s id="lost-73">I have stuff to do now... Bye, bye...</s>

<s id="CHOICE-HOSTESS">HOSTESS</s>
<s id="CHOICE-SLAVE">GIRL TO BE SOLD</s>

</strings>