<strings>
<s id="hug-1">Come here, baby... I'll give you what you want...</s>
<s id="hug-2">Hey... What... What the hell are you doing?</s>
<s id="hug-3">I'm doing exactly what you've been asking for... The way you've been exposing yourself to me... It's obvious you're craving for this...</s>
<s id="hug-4">No... I didn't ask for anything...</s>
<s id="hug-5">Come on... I know you're trying to make me go slower in the game by teasing me with this amazing body...</s>
<s id="hug-6">I loved your initiative, baby... Let me feel these titties of yours for a while... Don't you want to play another easy round?</s>
<s id="hug-7">No... Let me... go...</s>
<s id="hug-8">Yeah... Just hang in there a little more... You like my warm breath over your neck, don't you?</s>
<s id="hug-9">These tits feel so good... And your amazing ass rubbing on me... It's like my pants are going to explode...</s>
<s id="hug-10">Cut it out... It's enough...</s>
<s id="hug-11">Hey... Easy... This is getting so hot...</s>
<s id="hug-12">You need money right? How about I give you the next game prize without you even having to play?</s>
<s id="hug-13">What... What do you mean?</s>
<s id="hug-14">I mean this...</s>
<s id="hug-15">What the hel!?!</s>
<s id="hug-16">Come on... Give my boy down there a treat and I'll give a good prize...</s>
<s id="hug-17">Touch your... thing... for money?? How dare you...</s>
<s id="hug-18">I... I'm not a...</s>
<s id="hug-19">Oh, baby... I'm not calling you anything... Think of it as a simple exchange of favors... After all, you should know that my moves become super fast when I get such blue balls...</s>
<s id="hug-20">Now, come on... No one is watching... Just give me some good fun...</s>

<s id="touch-no-way">NO WAY</s>
<s id="touch-no-way-1">No... I can't do this... Just get off me...</s>
<s id="touch-no-way-2">Sigh... Such a tease...</s>
<s id="touch-no-way-3">Your loss, baby... Now my hands now feel faster than ever... Just try another round of bets to witness my true skill...</s>

<s id="touch-do">ACCEPT THE OFFER</s>
<s id="touch-do-1">I... I shouldn't, but... I need the money...</s>
<s id="touch-do-2">That's what I wanted to hear, baby... Now go ahead... Show me your true skill and you'll be well rewarded...</s>
<s id="touch-do-3">Oh boy... Such soft touch...</s>
<s id="touch-do-4">I... I can't beliebe I'm agreeing to this...</s>
<s id="touch-do-4-c">It's not like I never touch one of these anyways...</s>
<s id="touch-do-5">We're going to need some moves to make this work, baby...</s>
<s id="touch-do-6">Let'me show you...</s>
<s id="touch-do-7">Ahhh... You see what I'm talking about? I love fucking you little hand...</s>
<s id="touch-do-8">Oh baby... This is nice... I can spend hours like this...</s>
<s id="touch-do-9">What? No... Please... Just finish this already...</s>
<s id="touch-do-10">Well... If you want to speed this up, then how about help me a bit? I'd really appreciate...</s>
<s id="touch-do-11">Yeah, baby... That's it... You're the best...</s>
<s id="touch-do-12">I bet you're loving this country aren't you, baby? This is the place for you...</s>
<s id="touch-do-13">That's it... Hold it tight now!!!</s>
<s id="touch-do-14">Yeah... Thanks, baby... I needed that...</s>
<s id="touch-do-15">Just... Just get off me now...</s>
<s id="touch-do-16">Here... Take your prize... You definetively deserved it...</s>
<s id="touch-do-17">You know... A piece like you could make a lot of money around here like this...</s>
<s id="touch-do-18">I could be your... agent... It could be a dangerous line of work without a man to watch over you...</s>
<s id="touch-do-19">No... I... I just need to go now...</s>
<s id="touch-do-20-l">Goddamnit, <d character="Lara" suffix="..." /> You could have just pushed him away... Was that really necessary?</s>
<s id="touch-do-21-l">I'm... I'm sorry, <d character="Player" suffix="..." /> But... I didn't have a choice... We need the money...</s>
<s id="touch-do-22-l">Sigh... There's always another way, <d character="Lara" suffix="..." /></s>
<s id="touch-do-20-c">Jesus, <d character="Lara" suffix="..." /> Are you already having fun with the locals? Looks like you can't control yourself anymore...</s>
<s id="touch-do-21-c">I... wasn't having fun... I mean... I didn't have a choice... We need the money...</s>
<s id="touch-do-22-c">Yeah... Mixing pleasure and business sounds great, isn't?</s>

</strings>