<strings>
	<s id="creep">Oh Lord... I can't believe I'm allowing a creep take pictures of me like this...</s>
	<s id="can-hear">I can hear you, girl...</s>
	<s id="gave-boots">You only gave me my panties and boots... I thought you...</s>
	<s id="whining">And that's how you thank me? Panties and boots are a hot combo... Now stop whining and try to relax...</s>
	<s id="photographer">You know... I always wanted to work as a photographer before this job... I'd probably be much more successful if I had the opportunity to shoot hot models like you...</s>
	<s id="pro">Yeah... Looking beautiful...</s>
	<s id="embarassed">Hey... Your embarassed attitude made some cute frames, but I need some better poses now...</s>
	<s id="expect">You... You want me to make poses?!</s>
	<s id="of-course">Of course... I already said you to not worry... No one will see these pictures, except me and the collector...</s>
	<s id="backside">Now, come on... Show me that backside...</s>
	<s id="nice-one">Yeah... This is it...</s>
	<s id="fine-booty">Some big nice cheeks you have there, girl...</s>
	<s id="lose-panties">Now it's time to get rid of the panties...</s>
	<s id="you-said">What!?! But you said...</s>
	<s id="assets">Hey... We can't have a proper photo session without you showing the main 'assets'... So get the panties down...</s>
	<s id="now">Now!</s>
	
	<s id="OBEY">OBEY</s>
	<s id="REFUSE">REFUSE</s>

	<s id="obey-1">Good... You made the smart choice...</s>
	<s id="obey-2">Now, come on... The clock is ticking... Just pull it down...</s>
	<s id="obey-3">Yeah... It wasn't difficult, wast it?</s>
	<s id="obey-4">Now... Show me another good pose... If you want your clothes back, these photos must worth the price...  Lean there and make use of your modeling skills...</s>

	<s id="refuse-1">Sigh... You're really an annoying girl...</s>
	<s id="refuse-2">Then show me another good pose... If you want your clothes back, these photos must worth the price...  Lean there and make use of your modeling skills...</s>

	<s id="much-better">Yeah... Much better now...</s>
	<s id="buyer">Oh, man... I can already hear the lucrative offers I'll receive for you... I, mean... for your pictures...</s>

	<s id="lose-panties-offer">Come on now, girl... Drop the panties... I need hotter pictures...</s>
	<s id="lose-panties-but">But... but... I can't just stand here fully naked...</s>
	<s id="lose-panties-money">Look... How about this... Drop the panties and I will give you also some of my money... so you'll have a head start next time you try to recover your artifact playing cards with me...</s>

	<s id="ACCEPT">ACCEPT OFFER</s>

	<s id="offer-1">Good... You made the smart choice...</s>
	<s id="offer-2">Now, come on... You accepted the deal... Just pull it down...</s>
	<s id="offer-3">Yeah... It wasn't difficult, wast it?</s>

	<s id="feel-1">So... How does it feel?</s>
	<s id="feel-2">How... does it feel? What do you...</s>
	<s id="feel-3">You just dropped your panties for a man in exchange for money... Do you know how we call this?</s>
	<s id="feel-4">No... It's not like that... I... I just wanted to...</s>
	<s id="feel-5">Whatever... You can try to deny it, but you knew what you're doing... Let's keep working...</s>

	<s id="refuse-3">You're testing my patience, girl...</s>
	<s id="refuse-4">You better start making some good poses now to compensate...</s>

	<s id="panties-already-down">You are working like a pro, girl.... I loved the way you promptly dropped your panties when I asked... Now keep the pace and strike more sexy poses for me...</s>
	
	<s id="hang">Nice one.... You're definetively getting the hang of it, girl...</s>
	<s id="quit">You should quit the archaeology thing... Because anyone can see your real talent is to work on this...</s>
	<s id="one-more">One more!</s>
	<s id="pro">Oh, man... Look at this... She's a pro...</s>
	<s id="amazing">Just amazing...</s>
	<s id="wraps">Well... This one wraps our photo shoot...</s>

	<!-- High corruption -->
	<s id="done-already">Oh... Are we done, already?</s>
	<s id="memory-full">I'm sorry, girl... I can see you quickly took a fancy to sexy modeling and wanted more, but my memory card is already full of your pictures...</s>
	<s id="didnt-mean">No... I didn't mean that... I just want to know if...</s>
	<s id="denial">Yeah... You can keep yourself in denial, girl... But I can see you true self blooming behind the innocent attitude... You can take your clothes back...</s>

	<!-- Low corruption -->
	<s id="thank-god-over">Finally... Thank God this is over...</s>
	<s id="not-that-bad">Come on... It wasn't that bad... And I could almost see you having fun...</s>
	<s id="humiliating">It was just... humiliating...</s>
	<s id="take-back">Whatever... You can have your clothes back now...</s>

	<s id="finally">Sigh... I can finally get dressed again...</s>
	<s id="before-leave">Hey... Before you leave...</s>
	<s id="good-work">Here... This is for your good work...</s>
	<s id="speechless">I love it when they become speechless...</s>
	<s id="take-care-money">Now don't go spending all of it on drinks or gambling...</s>
	
	<s id="thanks-again">Thanks, girl... If you still want your precious artifact, we can always play again...</s>
	
</strings>