<string>
<s id="really-need">I... shouldn't be here like this... but... I don't know what else I can do...</s>
<s id="poor-thing">Poor thing... Don't lose hope...</s>
<s id="need-seal">...and I... I really need the seal...</s>
<s id="yeah-know">Yeah... I know...</s>
<s id="give-up">... and I... I can't give up now...</s>
<s id="giving-up">Giving up is for losers... And we're all winners here...</s>
<s id="came-far">...and I came from so far to...</s>

<s id="shhh">Shhh... It's okay, girl... There's no one else here to judge you...</s>

<s id="shaky">Jeez... You're all shaky, girl... Why are you so nervous?</s>
<s id="never">Because I... I never... I mean... I'm not used to...</s>
<s id="relax">Just relax and you will enjoy this too... It's like a dance... Just chill and follow my lead...</s>

<s id="stressed">You see? You seemed so stressed... And now I can already feel you getting lighter...</s>
<s id="hating">No... I... I'm hating this...</s>
<s id="hide-feel">Really... You don't need to hide how you feel, girl...</s>
<s id="not-hiding">I... I'm not hiding anything...</s>
<s id="sure">Are you sure you're not hiding?</s>
<s id="advantage">...you're just taking advantage of me... making me do these horrible things...</s>
<s id="so-horrible">Yeah... Sure... It's so horrible that you are still humping on me even after I stopped moving...</s>
<s id="scared">No, I... I was just scared of not doing what you told...</s>
<s id="closer">Yeah... Whatever helps you sleep at night, girl... Now let me come closer...</s>



<s id="feeling">Damn... I could spend all day just felling the shape of your body...</s>
<s id="moves">Your moves are great...</s>
<s id="nice-work">Nice work, girl... You got me prepped really fast...</s>
<s id="foreplay">Now... Enough of foreplay... It's time to have a good time...</s>
<s id="sure-1">Please... I'm not sure about this...</s>
<s id="nah-1">This is not the time for regrets, girl... Just relax and maybe you'll thank me later...</s>
<s id="sure-2">Oh my God... Oh my God...</s>
<s id="nah-2">Relax, girl... You'll thank me later...</s>

<s id="sexy">Whoa... You look so sexy like this...</s>
<s id="lie-table">A... A table... You're making me lie in table?</s>
<s id="furniture">Oh... I'm sorry... I still didn't find time to buy more furniture...</s>
<s id="nervous">Eeeeeasy, girl... You don't need to get so nervous...</s>
<s id="another-way">Please, sir... Is this really necessary? There must be another way to...</s>
<s id="shhhh2">Shhh... Don't worry, babe... I would never hurt you...</s>
<s id="touching">Fuck... Look at this beatiful pussy... Can you feel me touching it, girl?</s>
<s id="girl_">Girl?</s>
<s id="concentration">Do you really need all this concentration?</s>
<s id="start-slow">Well.. Let's start slowly and give it a trial...</s>
<s id="throbbing">Shiit... This tight litle pussy is throbbing down here...</s>
<s id="omg-3">Oh my God... Oh my God... Oh my God... Oh my God...</s>
<s id="praying">Keep praying, girl... The hardest part comes now...</s>
<s id="happend">Ooouuch... I... I can't believe it happened...</s>



<!-- Busted -->
<s id="cant-believe">I can't fucking believe this bitch...</s>
<s id="polite">I try to be polite... I offer you my hospitality... A place at my desk...</s>
<s id="retribute">And how do you retribute?</s>
<s id="FUCK-ME">TRYING TO FUCK WITH ME!!</s>
<s id="fucking">Well... I'll not disappointing you, though... I'll show you some well done fucking...</s>
<s id="no-sorry">_No... Please... I'm sorry... I'm sorry..._</s>

<s id="teach-you">Get these panties out of the way... I'll teach you what happens with people that try to mess with me...</s>
<s id="no-sorry-2">_I'm sorry... I'm sorry..._</s>

<s id="naked-whore">As you're already naked like a cheap whore, my work will be easier...</s>

<s id="now-come-here">Now, COME OVER HERE! You don't deserve foreplay... </s>
<s id="omg-no">_Oh my God... No, no, no..._</s>
<s id="happen">It is going to happen, girl... Just accept it...</s>
<s id="soft">My men have been soft with you... Only because they know I'm supposed to be one who have the first taste of any lost girl around here...</s>
<s id="harder">But now things will get harder to you... Literally...</s>
<s id="can-fell">This is a nice pussy... Can you feel me kissing its entrance?</s>
<s id="go-home">_I wanna go home... I wanna go home..._</s>
<s id="lets-check">Well... Let's check how easy it will be to get into...</s>
<s id="tight-one">Damn... You're a tight one...</s>
<s id="let-me-go">_Please, let me go... You're going to hurt me... Please..._</s>
<s id="leaving-sson">You'll be leaving soon... Just after learning your lesson...</s>
<s id="give-trinket">I'll even give you the damn trinket... You deserve it for having pussy like this... This will make you a little happier, wont it?</s>
<s id="here-go">I hope you're ready... Because here we go...</s>

<s id="noooo">nnnnhhhhggg... no.... Father.... I'm sorry...</s>


<!-- Drunk -->
<s id="you-ok">Are you okay, girl?</s>
<s id="shecond">I uuhh.. I jushht need a shecoond to... I... okay...</s>
<s id="dont-look-good">You don't look so good from here... You should go easier with the drinks...</s>
<s id="fuzzy">nnnhh.... hElLo yOu... it'ssh fUzZy hErE... and i hAte shQuarE eNiX... blOodY jAps doN uDershtNd mE...</s>
<s id="wasted">Damn... You're totally wasted... But, don't worry... As a gentleman, it's my duty to help you...</s>
<s id="trex">... geeeeNtLeMaan.... I wAnnA shooot a biiiiG t-rEx...</s>

<s id="heat">You know... Maybe it's not only the booze... All this heat is probably making you feel sick...</s>
<s id="clothes">Let us get off all the clothes you're wearing... It will certainly help you...</s>
<s id="fell-better">Yeah... I bet you'll fell better in no time...</s>
<s id="cold">Why... wHy itshh geTtiNg cOlDer hErE...</s>
<s id="lend-heat">Oh... I'm sorry... If it's too cold now, then let me lend you some body heat...</s>

<s id="naked">You all naked like this... The cold might be making you more dizzy...</s>
<s id="naked-heat">Let lend you some body heat...</s>

<s id="gorgeous">Yeah... So gorgeous...</s>
<s id="what-going">wHaat... whAaT iShh goInG on?</s>
<s id="fell-heat">This is amazing... Can you feel the heat, babe?</s>
<s id="dizzy">I'm... I feel soOo dIzZy...</s>
<s id="lay-table">Oh... Poor girl... If you're dizzy, the let me lay you donw here at this table...</s>
<s id="wait-lay">WaIt... Lay dOwN? WhY ?</s>
<s id="perfect">Don't worry... You'll be fine... And placed in the perfect position...</s>

<s id="what-doing">wHat... whAt aRe yoU doooInG... wHaT's gOiNg on...</s>
<s id="told-worry">Hey... I already told you to not worry... I'm just making sure you'll be okay...</s>
<s id="dangerous">It would be very dangerous for you to walk around in your current state...</s>
<s id="why-lying">bUt wHy I'm NakEd aNd lYinG oVer thIs tAblE... tHiS dOesN't fEeL rIghT...</s>
<s id="nice-kind">Shhh... Ain't I being nice and kind with you? Ain't I making you feel better?</s>
<s id="seems-so">... iT sEeMs To me, yEs...</s>
<s id="make-feel-better">And you wan't me to make you feel even better, right?</s>
<s id="less-dizzy">... I tsHinK sOoo... BuT mY heAd iS stIlL siPinnInG...</s>
<s id="really-good">Then just relax, there... I'll make you feel really good, now...</s>

<s id="beautiful-cooch">Yeah... Alcohol is a truly gift from the heavens... Look at this beautiful cooch...</s>
<s id="cant-resist">Oh boy... I just can't resist...</s>

<s id="feel-funny">Hey... I... I'm feElLinG sOmeThinG funny... wHaT arE yOu dOiNg?</s>
<s id="show-time">I'll just give you the best medicine in life... Just relax...</s>
<s id="probe">Let's do a little probing here...</s>

<s id="tight">Jesus... She is so tight... </s>
<s id="god-trying">Oh mY God... ArE you trYing to...</s>
<s id="can-stop">yOu can sTop... I'm feLling beTter... I'm feeLling beTter alReadY...</s>

<s id="just-minute">You will feel much better in just a minute, babe...</s>
<s id="no-please">No, pLeasE... No, pLeasE... _No, pLeasE..._</s>
<s id="here-come">Here I come...</s>

<s id="warm">Oh my God... You're so tight and warm...</s>
<s id="ouch-why">Ooouuch... Why... Why... why did you do that....</s>

<s id="cherry">Get outta here... Did I just popped your cherry?</s>
<s id="oh-no-no">Oh, no... no... nnnnhhhg...</s>
<s id="remember">Well... This definetively will be one to remember...</s>
<s id="dance">Now let's dance...</s>


<s id="pump-1">Damn, girl... You're so tight... If I knew the morning would end like this when I woke up today...</s>
<s id="KEEP-SILENT">KEEP SILENT</s>
<s id="ASK-STOP">ASK HIM TO END THIS</s>
<s id="ASK-EASY">ASK HIM TO GO EASY</s>

<s id="silent-1">Humm... Are you the silent type?</s>
<s id="silent-2">Oh come, on... I like hearing my girls moaning... or begging...</s>

<s id="stop-1">Please... Please... End this already...</s>
<s id="stop-2">End? What you mean?</s>
<s id="stop-3">Aahh... I got it... You like it fast and rough? Do you want me to speed up the pace? I'll grant your wish...</s>

<s id="easy-1">Please... Please... Go easy... Go easy...</s>
<s id="easy-2">Oh... Are you afraid I'll burst too eary and letting you craving for more? What a naughty girl...</s>
<s id="easy-3">No... I didn't mean that... I... I just...</s>
<s id="easy-4">Don't worry... You are really hot... But I can hadle it and give more time having fun...</s>

<s id="pump-2">Are you enjoying yourself, girl? Do you understand now what a good fucking is about?</s>

<s id="ASK-GO">ASK HIM TO LET GO</s>
<s id="TOO-ROUGH">SAY IT'S TOO ROUGH</s>

<s id="silent-3">Jesus Christ... You're hot, but very boring... I'll just finish this and give you a memento for you to think about silently...</s>

<s id="go-1">Please, let me go... Please....</s>
<s id="go-2">Oh.... Are you bored already and want to leave me?</s>
<s id="go-3">Then I will make you work for it... I'll just wait here for you to treat me good... And I can stay here the whole day until you show the skill to do it... </s>
<s id="go-4">Come on, girl... Make a move or we will stay here until night...</s>
<s id="go-5">Yeah... Fuck archaeology... This is your true call...</s>
<s id="go-6">You did it, girl... I can't hold it anymore...</s>

<s id="too-rough-1">nnnnghhh... Please... Its.... nnnnghhh... Too rough... This is too rough...</s>
<s id="too-rough-2">Yeah, babe... I can see this is how you like it...</s>
<s id="too-rough-3">Let's see if you can hold it...</s>
<s id="too-rough-4">Yeah... You shamelessly came taking a cock of a man you just met... You're natural born slut, girl...</s>
<s id="too-rough-5">No... I... I didn't want this... I... I'm hating this...</s>
<s id="too-rough-6">Whatever you say... Now it's my time...</s>

<s id="orgasm-1">Phew... That was good...</s>
<s id="orgasm-2">Oh my God... Did you... Did you... Inside of me?!?!?</s>
<s id="orgasm-3">Yep... There's a o lot of my swimmers inside you now... I'm sure you can feel the heat...</s>
<s id="orgasm-4">Oh no... Oh no...</s>
<s id="orgasm-5">Yeah... But I bet you're one of those prudent girls that are on the pill even when not screwing anyone...</s>
<s id="orgasm-6">I... I...</s>
<s id="orgasm-7">Whatever... You can have your clothes again...</s>

<s id="take-seal">And here... Take your precious artifact... You definetively worthed it...</s>
<s id="see-ya">I hope we can meet again, later... See ya...</s>

</string>
